<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.matt3756" name="Arcade Matt" version="3.0" provider-name="">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.routing" version="0.2.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.12.4"/>
        <import addon="plugin.video.youtube"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="qazwsxedc.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Arcade Matt Youtube</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Hey, I'm Arcade Matt and welcome to my arcade channel! I like to go out to arcades and play the claw machine, some people also call them a skill crane or crane game. I even show tips and tricks on how to win at them! I don't use any cheat or hack, just skill to come out a winner! I enjoy the coin pusher for quarters and bonus coin wins! I'm also a fan of arcade ticket games, found at places like Dave and Busters, Round One, and Tilt arcades. I love to win the arcade jackpot for tons of tickets! I then use my tickets to get awesome prizes like a GoPro, Nintendo Consoles, and more! Jackpot ticket games I enjoy playing are Slam a Winner, Dizzy Chicken, Tower of Tickets, Monster Drop, Pop the Lock, among others! Many of these games are 100% skill! I also enjoy prize games like Stacker, Sega Keymaster, Winner's Cube,  where you can win high end prizes like an Ipad, Xbox, PS4, or even money like a $100 bill! I've also branched out to carnival games and mini golf! SUB TODAY!
		</description>
        <language>en pt</language>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-3.0</license>
        <news></news>
        <disclaimer>The author of this add-on is in no way affiliated with Arcade Matt Youtuber</disclaimer>
        <assets>
        <icon>resources/images/icon.png</icon>
        <fanart>resources/images/fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
